{
    "id": "093be4bfa23b44fb99bd7a15e2bde0dd",
    "title": "Will Or Going To",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I can’t lift this box. OK. I ………………… help you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "am going to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fb4d3838677c4c76a1558fd6f8558677"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t think that she …………………… recognize me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "is going to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d3017f6c93174f99aafac56d2acc8aa7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Careful! You ………………… fall.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "are going to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e2255b19fb6e47f0863db9e02f9bedd7"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………….. graduate next year.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "is going to",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "492408c3900349bf98539283e0c0dde3"
        },
        {
            "question": "The flight …………………… at 9 pm.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "departs",
                "will depart"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6c224df56e854036826f7583a23a60e8"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………. meet your dad tomorrow afternoon.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am going to",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4b1d31403d9647abb0878086bb19e251"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is very hard-working. I think he ........................................ be very successful.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "is going to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d1503463ee444c24a7419d1fc5857c97"
        },
        {
            "question": "..................................... you marry me?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Will",
                "Are you going to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c8c5f1f874c640e3b00b649ea06f84ec"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who do you think …………………….. win the championship?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "is going to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9844a140a55243b3b017f45ee8473b05"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… to America next month.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "fly",
                "will fly",
                "am flying"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4fff301eece642f998d4c362ba0152ae"
        }
    ]
}